The Hierarchy in Unity is a complete list of any object in your open scene.
Unity の Hierarchy ビューはシーンにおける完全なオブジェクトの一覧です。
Objects are listed from A to Z order,
オブジェクトは A から Z まで順番に並べれています。
but it is also possible to create hierarchies of objects
しかし、オブジェクトの階層を作成して
which are in turn listed in A to Z order.
その中で A から Z まで順番に表示することも出来ます。
Hierarchies of objects mean that they are grouped, with the top most object being called the Parent Object
オブジェクトの階層とは、グルーピングが行われて、もっとも上にあるオブジェクトを親オブジェクトと呼びます。
and the rest being referred to as Children or Child objects.
そして残りのオブジェクトを子または子オブジェクトと呼びます。
These objects then have their transform values based upon that of their parent object.
これらの表示されたオブジェクトの Transform の値は親オブジェクトにもとづきます。
For example the position of an object when loose in the hierarchy
例えば、Hierarchy ビューで独立したオブジェクトの位置は
is based on it's distance from the world origin, or zero point.
原点、すなわちゼロ地点からの距離にもとづきます。
But when this object is made a child of another object it's position is relative to that of it's parent.
しかし、オブジェクトが別オブジェクトの子オブジェクトとした場合、その位置は親に対して相対的になります。
In this example the character object is at the origin of the 3D scene,
次の例では、キャラクターオブジェクトは3D 座標の原点にあります。
the position (0, 0, 0).
位置 は (0, 0, 0) です。
And there is a cube object at position (5, 1, 5).
さらにキューブオブジェクトが (5, 1, 5) にあります。
But when the character object is made a child of the cube - it's origin, or zero point,
もしキャラクターオブジェクトがキューブの子オブジェクトとした場合、この原点またはゼロ地点
is then the position of the parent object, the cube.
は親オブジェクト、すなわちの位置になります。
Now the character's position is said to be (-5, -1, -5).
キャラクターの位置は (-5, -1, -5) となりました。
This being the distance from the cube object, it's parent and therefore it's origin position.
これはキューブオブジェクト、すなわち親オブジェクト、すなわち原点からの距離です。
We can also see that with Pivot Point Rotation enabled
Pivot Point Rotation が有効化されてるので、
the rotation is now based on the parent object
Rotation がもとづくのが、子オブジェクトの軸ではなく、
rather than rotating around it's own axis.
親オブジェクトとなっていることが確認できます。
The same then applies to movement,
同じことが動作にも
and scaling.
スケールにもいえます。
And this will apply until that object is no longer a child.
そしてこれはオブジェクトが子オブジェクトでなくなるまで適用され続けます。
Other features of the hierarchy are the Create button
Hierarchy の他の機能は Create ボタンおよび
and Search field.
検索フィールドです。
The create button on the hierarchy acts as a mirror of the Game Object - Create Other top menu
Hierarchy の Create ボタンはメニューの Game Object - Create Other と同等の動きをして、
and this will allow you to create various different things that you will need to construct your games in Unity.
これにより、Unityでゲームを構築するのに必要な様々なものを作成できるようになります。
Whilst the search field works in a similar way to the search field in the Scene view,
検索フィールドはシーンビューの検索と同様の動きをして、
allowing you to narrow down objects using their name.
名前による絞込みを行うことが出来ます。
The scene view then reacts by greying out other objects
絞込みにより、シーンビューは他のオブジェクトをグレーアウトして
allowing you to see the object you've searched for more easily.
検索したオブジェクトをより容易にみつけることが出来ます。
You can also make use of the modifier T: in order to search for types of object.
さらに T: 修飾子を活用ｓるうことでオブジェクトの型を検索することが出来ます。
Type here being considered as one of the objects components.
ここに入力した内容はオブジェクトコンポーネントのひとつとしてみなすことが出来ます。
For example if I search for T:Light
例えばもし T:Light として検索すると
there is only one light in my current scene,
現在のシーンにはひとつのライトしかなく、
one on the end of the players gun.
ひとつはプレイヤーの銃の端にあります。
And if I search for T: Audio Source
もし T: Audio Source とすると、
I'll be narrowed down to 3 objects,
3 つのオブジェクトに絞込みが行われて、
the only ones in the scene that happen to have audio source components attached to them.
これはシーン上の Audio Source コンポーネントをアタッチされているオブジェクトのみです。
When searching in this way, the bottom of the hierarchy shows the path to the object that you've found.
このように検索することで、Hierarchy の最下部はみつけたオブジェクトのパス表示をします。
Damage audio source being the one I have selected,
この場合、選択したのは Damage Audio Source です。
Player being it's parent and Cube being the parent of that object.
Player がこの親であり、Cube はさらにこのオブジェクトの親になります。
This means that when cancelling the search you can easily see where your object is.
いいかえると、検索をキャンセルした後もオブジェクトがどこにあるか容易にみつけることが出来ます。
It will also remain selected and the parent objects of that object will be expanded to show where it's located.
選択された状態は継続して、そのオブジェクトの親オブジェクトがどの場所にあるか表示されます。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)